Dan Moldea investigative journalism collection, 1937-2008
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Dan Moldea investigative journalism collection
1937-2008
C0281
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
15 linear ft. (15 boxes)
Dan Moldea investigative journalism collection consits of resesarch files for six of Dan Moldea's books. The files include research on "Hoffa Wars," "Dark Victory: Ronald Reagan, MCA, and the Mob," "The Killing of Robert F. Kennedy," "Washington Tragedy: How the Suicide of Vincent Foster Ignited a Political Firestorm," "Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer," and "The Hunting of Cain."
Moldea, Dan E., 1950-
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Dan Moldea in 2015 and 2016.
Biographical Information
Dan Moldea has been an independent investigative journalist specializing on organized crime and political corruption investigations since 1974, as well as a best-selling author who has published eight nonfiction books: "The Hoffa Wars" ( 1978); "The Hunting of Cain: A True Story of Money, Greed, and Fratricide" (1983); "Dark Victory: Ronald Reagan, MCA, and the Mob" (1986); "Interference: How Organized Crime Influences Professional Football" (1989); "The Killing of Robert F. Kennedy" (1995); "Evidence Dismissed: The Inside Story of the Police Investigation of O.J. Simpson" (with Tom Lange and Philip Vannatter, 1997); and "A Washington Tragedy: How the Suicide of Vincent Foster Ignited a Political Firestorm" (1998). He recently published his memoir "Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer: Adventures in the Jungles of Crime, Politics and Journalism" (2013).
Scope and Content
Dan Moldea investigative journalism collection consits of resesarch files for six of Dan Moldea's books. The files include research on "Hoffa Wars," "Dark Victory: Ronald Reagan, MCA, and the Mob," "The Killing of Robert F. Kennedy," "Washington Tragedy: How the Suicide of Vincent Foster Ignited a Political Firestorm,""Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer," and "The Hunting of Cain." The files are largely arranged by book chapter and by subject.
Arrangement
Organized into four series.
Series 1: "Hoffa Wars," 1954-2001 (Boxes 1-3)
Series 2: "Dark Victory: Ronald Reagan, MCA, and the Mob" research, 1937-1997 (Boxes 4-5)
Series 3: "The Killing of Robert F. Kennedy" research, 1950s-2008 (Boxes 6-7)
Series 4: "Washington Tragedy: How the Suicide of Vincent Foster Ignited a Political Firestorm" research, 1992-2007 (Boxes 8-9)
Series 5: "Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer" research, 1962-2013 (Boxes 10-14)
Series 6: "The Hunting of Cain" research, 1977-1981 (Box 15)
Related Material
Special Collections Research Center holds the that includes photographs of Robert F. Kennedy and Jimmy Hoffa.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Murder.; Organized crime.
Contents List
- Series 1: "Hoffa Wars" research, 1954-2001; (3 boxes)
  - One, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Two, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Three, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Three - Kefauver Hearings, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Four - Bender Hearings, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Four - Trust Agreement, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Five, 1958 - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Six, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Seven - Kohn/Rolling Stone Story, 1976 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Seven - Irv Davidson, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Eight, 1962 - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Eight, 1954 - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Eight - Chavez, 1958 - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Eight - Shulman, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Eight - McLendon, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Nine, 1965 - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ten, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Eleven - Teammate, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Twelve, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Twelve, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Thirteen, 1960s - 1970s (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fourteen, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fourteen - Dininger Statement, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Fourteen, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fifteen - McQuaide, 1973 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fifteen - negotiating committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fifteen - committee, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fifteen, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fifteen - Litigation, 1971 - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fifteen - T.U.R.F., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fifteen - Teamster, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fifteen - letters, 1971 - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sixteen - IBT Organizing Drive, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sixteen - Capitol Hill News Service, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Seventeen - James P. Hoffa, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Eighteen - letters, 1973 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Eighteen - articles, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Eighteen - 10th anniversary, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nineteen, 1974 - 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Twenty - contacts, 1975 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Twenty One - Nixon and the Hoffa Pardon, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Twenty One - Hoffa and Watergate, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Twenty One - FBI key interviews, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Twenty One - Detroit News, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Twenty One, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Twenty One - Hoffa Overdrive articles, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Twenty One - Hoffa Wars pictures, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Twenty One - newspapers, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Twenty Two - Hoffa investigation, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Twenty Three, August 28, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Twenty Four, September 22, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Twenty Five, October 31, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Twenty Six, December 22, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Twenty Seven, 1976 - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Series 2: "Dark Victory: Ronald Reagan, MCA, and the Mob" research, 1937-1997; (2 boxes)
  - Chapter One - Posner, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chapter One - Articles, 1940 - 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chapter One - Articles, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chapter One - James C. Petrillo, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chapter One - American Federation of Musicians, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Two - Bioff, 1967 - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Two - JD Reports, 1941 - 1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Three - MCA Management Contracts, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chapter Three - Ballroom Operators and Promoters, 1930s - 1940s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chapter Three - MCA Clients, 1941 - 1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chapter Four, 1940 - 1943 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chapter Five - Hayward, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chapter Five - William Morris Agency, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chapter Five - JD Reports, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chapter Five - MCA, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chapter Five - General Amusement Corporation, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chapter Five - Frederick Brothers, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chapter Five - Herman Bennett, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chapter Five - Hollywood Palladium, 1944 - 1946 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chapter Six - Artists, 1945 - 1946 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chapter Six - Billy McDonald, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chapter Seven - Paul Mantz, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Chapter Eight, 1953 - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Chapter Nine - "Star Spangled Octopus", 1946 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Chapter Nine - Reports, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chapter Ten, 1947 - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Los Angeles court, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - JD Reports, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - JD Reports, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Chapter Twelve, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Chapter Thirteen, 1952 - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Chapter Fourteen - JD Reports, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Chapter Fourteen - Reagan and 6E, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Chapter Fourteen - MCA Memorandum, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chapter Fourteen - Hoven (Ciro's) vs. MCA, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapter Fourteen - repeal of gambling taxes, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chapter Fifteen, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Chapter sixteen - JD Reports, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Chapter sixteen - JD Reports, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Chapter Seventeen - MCA/Universal Pictures, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Chapter Seventeen - investigation of MCA, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Chapter Nineteen - Strike, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Chapter Twenty - Files, 1960 - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Chapter Twenty - MCA/Warner, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Chapter Twenty - JD Reports, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Chapter Twenty-One - JD Documents, 1960 - 1961 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Chapter Twenty-Two - MCA-SAG Agreement, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Chapter Twenty-Two - Conference with Zapple, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Chapter Twenty-Two - JD Reports, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Chapter Twenty-Four - Court Transcript, July 16, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - US vs. MCA: temporary restraining order, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - US vs. MCA: preliminary injunction motion, July 16, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - Stanley Disney affidavit, July 16, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - Lew Wasserman affidavit, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - Allen Sunsman affidavit, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - Index of Files US vs. MCA, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - film releases by Universal, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - US vs. MCA: final judgement, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - affidavit supporting plaintiff, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - US vs. MCA: Stipulation and Orders, September 18, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - Plaintiff's memorandum, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Chapter Twenty-Five - US vs. MCA: Complaint, July 13, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Chapter Twenty-Six - lawyer letters, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Twenty-Six - articles, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Twenty-Seven - Friar's Club, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Twenty-Eight, 1973 - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Twenty-Nine - Coleman, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Thirty, 1960s - 1970s (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Thirty-One, 1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Thirty-Two - news article, June 6, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chapter Thirty-Three, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chapter Thirty-Four - Mike Curb, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chapter Thirty-Five, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - News articles, 1960s - 1980s (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - MCA to file - The Bistro, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - MCA to file - Reagan and GE, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - MCA to file - Reagan finances articles, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - MCA to file - Reagan Presidential Foundation, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - MCA to file - Danica Enterprises, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - MCA to file - statement of claim, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - MCA to file - MCA stockholders report, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - MCA to file - JD reports, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - MCA to file - Bioff testimony, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - MCA to file - former MCA employees, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - MCA to file - MCA-Decca, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - MCA to file - articles, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - MCA to file - Decca files, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Greg Bautser, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Korshak: background, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Dark Victory, 1996 - 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Korshak, 1962 - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Korshak, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sid Sheinberg, 1987 - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Contra drugs, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Lew Wasserman's death, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - William French Smith, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - OC - general, 1970s - 1980s (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Ray Donovan, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - William Casey, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - DV - to be filed, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Series 3: "The Killing of Robert F. Kennedy" research, 1950s-2008; (2 boxes)
  - Preface - RFK pix, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Prologue, 1980s - 1990s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - One - RFK's last speech, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - One - Sirhan's movements, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Two, 1968, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Three, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Four - NYT on Time Warner, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Five, July 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Six, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Seven, 1968 - 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Eight, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Nine, 1960s - 1980s (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ten - Pena, 1960s - 1970s (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ten - Henry Rainistella, 1968 - 1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Eleven - Parsons/Cooper, 1967 - 1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Eleven - Hernandez, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Eleven - Sharaga, 1974 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Twelve, 1950s - 1970s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Thirteen, 1970s - 1980s (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fourteen, 1960s - 1980s (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fifteen - Simson Affidavit, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Sixteen - RFK em-general, July 3, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sixteen - extra bullets witnesses, 1960s - 1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sixteen - Greiner/Fernandez, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sixteen - bullet accounting, July 8, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sixteen - Joling letter to Melanson, December 23, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Seventeen - re-testing of exhibits - Sirhan, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Seventeen - firearm info, 1970s - 1990s (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Eighteen - pantry raid, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Eighteen - Kranz report, 1975 - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Nineteen, 1985 - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Twenty - ACE Guard Service, 1960s - 1980s (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Twenty-One - Yoder, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Twenty-Two, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Twenty-Three, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Twenty-four, 1968, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Twenty-Five, 1960s - 1980s (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Twenty-Six - Stone v. FBI, 1980s - 1990s (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Twenty-Eight, June 19, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970s - 1990s (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Epilogue, 1960s - 1990s (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous - witness list, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous - Sandra Serrano, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous - William Bailey FBI, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Miscelaneous - Godfrey Hodgson, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous - Ted Charach, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous - Greg Stone suicide, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous - Pete Hamill, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Series 4: "Washington Tragedy: How the Suicide of Vincent Foster Ignited a Political Firestorm" research, 1992-2007; (2 boxes)
  - I. 1., 1993 - 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - I. 2., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - I. 3., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - I. 4., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - I. 5., 1993 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - I. 6., 1990s (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - I. 7., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - I. 8., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - I. 9., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - I. 10., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - I. 11., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - I. 12., 1993 - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - I. 13., July 22, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - I. 14., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - I. 15., 1993 - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - I. 16., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - I. 17., July 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - I. 18., Juy 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - I. 19., 1993 - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - I. 20., July 1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - I. 21., July 20, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - I. 22., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - I. 23., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - I. 24., August 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - I. 25., August 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - I. 26., August 1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - I. 27., 1992 - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - I. 28., 1993 - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - I. 29., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - II. 1., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - II. 2., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - II. 3., February 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - II. 4., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - II. 5., February 1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - II. 6., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - II. 7., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - II. 8., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - II. 9., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - II. 10., 1993 - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - II. 11., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - II. 12., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - II. 13., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - II. 14., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - II. 15., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - II. 16., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - II. 17., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - II. 18., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - II. 19., June 12, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - II. 20., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - II. 21., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - II. 22., July 1994 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - II. 23., July 1994 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - II. 24., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - II. 25., 1993 - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - II. 26., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - II. 27., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - III. 1., 1994 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - III. 2., 1994 - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - III. 3., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - III. 4., 1994 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - III. 5., 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - III. 6., 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - III. 7., July 1995 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - III. 8., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - III. 9., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - III. 10., August 1995 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - III. 11., September 1995 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - III. 12., 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - III. 13., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - III. 14., 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - III. 15., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - III. 16., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - III. 17., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - III. 18., 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - III. 19., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - III. 20., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - III. 21., 1994 - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - III. 22., October 1997 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - III. 23., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Foster, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - OIC leaks, 1994 - 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Reviews for A Washington Tragedy, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Foster talking points, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Starr, Kenneth (appointment and background), 1994 - 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Regnery bio, 1989 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Knowlton, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Talking Heads, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chris Ruddy, 1996 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hugh Sprunt, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ambrose articles, 1995 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - WJC, January 22, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Reed Irvine, 1995 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Wall Street Journal, August 18, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chronologies, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Richard Scaife, 2005 - 2007 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ken Star, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - David Sentelle, 1990s - 2000s (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Starr's ex-prosecution in OIC, 2001 - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Starr allegations, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous - to be filed, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous - post-Foster material, 1998 - 2000s (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous - photos, diagrams, illustrations, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Rolla reports, 1993 - 1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Renee Apt reports, May 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Ferstl reports, 1993 - 1994 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Fornshill FBI reports, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Simonello reports, 1993 - 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Braun's ESPP / FBI reports, 1993 - 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Haut, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wayne Johnson, June 1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Julie Spetz, May 1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Christine Hodakievic, May 1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Corey Ashford, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Medical examiners, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Ambulance one / FBI reports, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Engine one / FBI reports, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Truck one / FBI reports, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Medic one / FBI reports, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Jim Hamilton, January 5, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Series 5: "Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer" research, 1962-2013; (5 boxes)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Prologue, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.1, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.2, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.3, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.4, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.5, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.6, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.7, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.8, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.9, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.10, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.11, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.12, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.13, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Confessions a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 1.14, 2000 - 2013 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bound Documents Pertaining to Modea's Career in Chronological Order with Tabs, 1962 - 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1972 CDF Ledger (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 2.1, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 2.2, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 2.3, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.6, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.7, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.8, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.9, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.11, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.12, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 3.13, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.1, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.2, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.3, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.4, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.5, 2000-2013 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 4.6, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.1, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.2, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.3, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.4, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.5, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.7, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.8, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.9, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.10, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 5.11, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.1, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.2, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.3, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.4, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.5, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.6, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 6.7, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.1, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 19)